title,summary,keywords,phrases,entities,sentiment,sentiment_label,time_published,risk_factor
"Evaluating Apple Against Peers In Technology Hardware, Storage & Peripherals Industry - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","In the fast-paced and cutthroat world of business, conducting thorough company analysis is essential for investors and industry experts. In this article, we will undertake a comprehensive industry comparison, evaluating Apple AAPL in comparison to its major competitors within the Technology ...",[],[],"[('Storage & Peripherals Industry - Apple', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.258208,positive,20250818T150055,low
"How To Trade SPY And Top Tech Stocks Today - Meta Platforms  ( NASDAQ:META ) , Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ",Today's economic calendar launches the week with a modest set of releases that could set a cautious tone for trading. The New York Fed Services Business Activity for August will provide a snapshot of regional service sector performance.,[],[],"[('Today - Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'PERSON'), ('The New York Fed Services Business Activity', 'ORG')]",0.024744,positive,20250818T140200,low
"OpenAI, Other Tech Firms Bypass American Workers, Favor H-1B Candidates Through Discriminatory Job Postings: Report - Meta Platforms  ( NASDAQ:META ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Major tech companies have been accused of using local newspaper job ads to target immigrant workers for green cards, potentially bypassing H-1B laws. Companies with H-1B employees in the green card process are said to be running local newspaper ads to appeal to immigrant job seekers.",[],[],"[('Tech Firms Bypass American Workers', 'ORG'), ('Favor H-1B Candidates Through Discriminatory Job Postings', 'ORG'), ('Report - Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",-0.016531,negative,20250818T133632,low
Here is What to Know Beyond Why Apple Inc.  ( AAPL )  is a Trending Stock,"Recently, Zacks.com users have been paying close attention to Apple (AAPL). This makes it worthwhile to examine what the stock has in store.",[],[],"[('a Trending Stock', 'ORG'), ('Zacks.com', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.242082,positive,20250818T130003,low
Invest Like Warren Buffett With These ETFs,"Buffett's Berkshire reshapes its portfolio with big bets on UnitedHealth and housing, while trimming Apple and Bank of America. The big bets put focus on ETFs like IHF and ITB.",[],[],"[('Invest', 'ORG'), ('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), (""Buffett's Berkshire"", 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Bank of America', 'ORG'), ('IHF', 'ORG'), ('ITB', 'ORG')]",0.248808,positive,20250818T104500,low
Should Schwab Fundamental U.S. Large Company ETF  ( FNDX )  Be on Your Investing Radar?,Style Box ETF report for ...,[],[],"[('Schwab Fundamental', 'ORG'), ('Style Box', 'PERSON')]",0.221653,positive,20250818T102002,low
"The Most Anticipated Stock Splits of 2025 May Be Members of the ""Magnificent Seven""","Among Nvidia, Microsoft, Apple, Alphabet, Amazon, Meta Platforms, and Tesla are two sensational businesses that can become Wall Street's next blockbuster stock-split stocks.",[],[],"[('The Most Anticipated Stock Splits', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'ORG')]",0.31303,positive,20250818T075100,low
"Google Slapped With $36 Million Fine Amid Anti-Competitive Practices In Australia - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOG ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ",Alphabet's Google GOOG GOOGL has agreed to pay a hefty fine of $36 million in Australia. This comes after allegations of anti-competitive practices involving the country's two largest telecom companies. ArrivedBuy shares of homes and vacation rentals for as little as $100. Get Started,[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG'), (""Alphabet's Google GOOG GOOGL"", 'ORG'), ('ArrivedBuy', 'ORG')]",0.069724,positive,20250818T075019,low
Prediction: These 3 Artificial Intelligence  ( AI )  Stocks Will Be Worth Over $10 Trillion by 2035,Ten years. $10 trillion. Easy peasy?,[],[],"[('These 3 Artificial Intelligence  (', 'ORG'), ('Will Be', 'PERSON')]",0.318045,positive,20250818T075000,low
"Billionaire Warren Buffett Sold 41% of Berkshire's Stake in Bank of America and Is Piling Into a Famed Consumer Brand That's Soared 7,200% Since Its IPO","The Oracle of Omaha has sent more than 427 million shares of Bank of America to the chopping block since mid-July 2024, and he continues to build his company's stake in a well-known, consumer-facing company.",[],[],"[('Warren Buffett Sold', 'PERSON'), (""Berkshire's Stake"", 'ORG'), ('Bank of America', 'ORG'), ('Bank of America', 'ORG')]",0.27635,positive,20250818T070600,low
Apple's Vision Pro Struggles To Gain Traction Amid Slow Release Of Immersive Video - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ,"Apple's Vision Pro headset struggles to captivate users with high prices and limited immersive video content. Future upgrades loom on the horizon, but the slow pace of innovation casts doubt on the product's longevity.",[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.124842,positive,20250817T195116,low
3 No-Brainer Warren Buffett Stocks to Buy Right Now,Each of these companies has robust long-term opportunities.,[],[],"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON')]",0.309107,positive,20250817T180500,low
"Peter Lynch: 'Stock Market Has Been The Best Place To Be, But If You Need Money In 1 or 2 Years, You Shouldn't Be Buying Stocks' - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOGL ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Lynch emphasizes the virtue of patience, highlighting long-term investment as the key for retirement planning. Looking beyond the giants, Lynch advises finding potential in excellent companies within struggling sectors. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise ...",[],[],"[('Peter Lynch', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Lynch', 'ORG')]",0.305453,positive,20250817T174627,low
"Coca-Cola, Amazon, Google, And Nvidia Have Used This Startup's AI Avatars - Inside Jeff Lu's $40M Rise To America's Fastest-Growing Company - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Adobe  ( NASDAQ:ADBE ) ","In the same Palo Alto, California, building where Mark Zuckerberg grew Facebook in 2005, Jeff Lu now leads Akool, the generative AI platform that has created lifelike avatars for Coca-Cola KO, Amazon AMZN, Google, and Nvidia NVDA. The company ranks No. 1 on this year's Inc. 5000 list, Inc. reports.",[],[],"[('Coca-Cola', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), (""AI Avatars - Inside Jeff Lu's"", 'ORG'), ('Fastest-Growing Company - Apple', 'ORG'), ('Adobe  ', 'PERSON'), ('Mark Zuckerberg', 'PERSON'), ('Jeff Lu', 'PERSON'), ('Akool', 'ORG'), ('Coca-Cola KO', 'ORG'), ('Amazon AMZN', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Nvidia NVDA', 'ORG'), ('Inc.', 'ORG')]",0.144115,positive,20250817T163146,low
Warren Buffett Is Selling Apple and Bank of America Stock and Piling Into an Embattled Healthcare Stock Down 46% This Year,"Berkshire Hathaway recently filed its second-quarter 13F form, revealing its stock holdings at the end of June.",[],[],"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Bank of America Stock', 'ORG'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON')]",0.081731,positive,20250817T152300,low
Apple Accidentally Exposes Top-Secret Hardware Plans Across Seven Product Lines - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ,"Apple's code slip-up reveals a sneak peek into its tech future, from iPhones to a new Vision Pro. Details in software code hint at major upgrades for Apple TV, Studio Display, and a host of other devices. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise into opportunity.",[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('iPhones', 'ORG'), ('Vision Pro', 'ORG'), ('Apple TV', 'ORG'), ('Studio Display', 'PERSON')]",0.106031,positive,20250817T133110,low
"Consumer Tech News  ( August 11-August 15 ) : Consumer Sentiment Slips, Stimulus Sparks Rallies, and Cisco & Applied Materials Headline Earnings - Advance Auto Parts  ( NYSE:AAP ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","U.S. sentiment dips on inflation worries, while China's stimulus boosts stocks and fuels global market optimism. Cisco and Applied Materials beat earnings estimates, capping a mixed season influenced by shifting macro trends.",[],[],"[('Consumer Tech News', 'ORG'), ('Sentiment Slips', 'PERSON'), ('Cisco & Applied Materials Headline Earnings - Advance Auto Parts  ', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Applied Materials', 'ORG')]",0.093983,positive,20250817T132121,low
"Meet the Marvelous Vanguard ETF With 57.7% of Its Portfolio Invested in the ""Magnificent Seven"" Stocks","This Vanguard exchange-traded fund can help investors beat the S&P 500, but it comes with risks.",[],[],[],0.250038,positive,20250817T103100,low
Can New AI-Powered Devices Propel Apple Stock Higher?,Apple is looking to change the narrative that it's no longer a technology innovator.,[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.228187,positive,20250817T081000,low
"'That's Something We Didn't Quite Anticipate': The Moto X, And Why Former Motorola CEO Says Building Smartphones In The US Is Nearly Impossible - Motorola Solutions  ( NYSE:MSI ) ","In 2013, Motorola became the first company to attempt to produce smartphones domestically Its Texas factory only remained open for one year before production returned overseas Dennis Woodside, the company's CEO at the time, highlighted workforce shortages as the primary reason the experiment ...",[],[],"[('Motorola', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('Motorola', 'ORG'), ('Dennis Woodside', 'PERSON')]",0.06651,positive,20250817T010110,low
Where Will Apple Stock Be in 5 Years?,"Apple stock hasn't moved this year, but it isn't the first time the market has soured on it.",[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.055063,positive,20250816T220500,low
"Along With $100 Billion U.S. Manufacturing Commitment, Apple's Tim Cook Gifted Trump A Glass 'Made In USA' Plaque On 24-Karat Gold - Corning  ( NYSE:GLW ) ","Apple AAPL CEO Tim Cook earned the title of ""tech's Trump whisperer"" in the president's first term, and he just may have shown why. Cook gifted President Donald Trump a glass plaque with a 24-karat gold base on Aug. 6.",[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Tim Cook Gifted', 'PERSON'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Tim Cook', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Cook', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]",0.348087,positive,20250816T200223,low
BMNR: The Big Ethereum Opportunity Wall Street Can't Ignore,The history of the stock market is always written by the biggest winners. They set the precedent for every newcomer looking to disrupt the old guard stocks that came before. They create the expectations that traders use to price the markets.,[],[],"[('The Big Ethereum Opportunity Wall Street', 'ORG')]",0.23363,positive,20250816T120500,low
"After Gaining $394 Billion in Market Cap in 3 Days, Is Apple Stock on Its Way to Joining Nvidia and Microsoft in the $4 Trillion Club?","Apple is closing in on $3.5 trillion in market cap, but it could take time to reach $4 trillion.",[],[],"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.212989,positive,20250816T110900,low
Apple's 10% Stock Pop: Time to Invest in the Technology Giant Embracing America?,The company is adding a new $100 billion investment in the United States.,[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Invest', 'ORG')]",0.136086,positive,20250816T071200,low
"David Tepper's Hedge Fund Bets On Intel, UnitedHealth; Cuts Position In Four Mag 7 Stocks - Alibaba Gr Hldgs  ( NYSE:BABA ) ","David Tepper's Appaloosa decreased position sizes in several Magnificent 7 stocks in the second quarter. The company increased its position in UnitedHealth Group with size, making it the top position.",[],[],"[(""David Tepper's"", 'PERSON'), ('Hedge Fund Bets', 'ORG'), ('Intel', 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), (""David Tepper's"", 'PERSON'), ('UnitedHealth Group', 'ORG')]",0.192542,positive,20250815T195929,low
"Taiwan Semiconductor's Fading Hot Streak Raises Stakes For Direxion's TSM-Focused Bull, Bear Funds - NVIDIA  ( NASDAQ:NVDA ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Pure-play foundry Taiwan Semiconductor has been on a hot streak since April, though the rally has decelerated. Trajectory questions shines an intriguing spotlight on Direxion's TSM-focused bull and bear ETFs. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise into ...",[],[],"[(""Taiwan Semiconductor's"", 'ORG'), ('Bear Funds - NVIDIA', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan Semiconductor', 'ORG')]",0.134788,positive,20250815T185723,low
"Warren Buffett's Top 10 Berkshire Bets Span Apple, Coca-Cola, Finance And Oil - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , American Express  ( NYSE:AXP ) ",A look at the top 10 stock holdings in Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway portfolio. The top 10 holdings have underperformed stock market indexes in 2025. Get the latest proven ETF strategies to target and profit from summer volatility before the next big market swing.,"[('profit', 'positive')]",[],"[(""Warren Buffett's"", 'PERSON'), ('Top 10 Berkshire Bets Span Apple', 'ORG'), ('Coca-Cola, Finance', 'ORG'), ('Oil - Apple', 'ORG'), ('American Express', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), (""Warren Buffett's"", 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON')]",0.195941,positive,20250815T163928,low
Apple's $500 Billion Investment Into America Just Got Larger: Does That Mean You Should Buy the Stock?,Investors are missing the big picture with Apple's business today.,[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.094022,positive,20250815T160000,low
"Performance Comparison: Apple And Competitors In Technology Hardware, Storage & Peripherals Industry - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Amidst the fast-paced and highly competitive business environment of today, conducting comprehensive company analysis is essential for investors and industry enthusiasts.",[],[],"[('Performance Comparison', 'PERSON'), ('Storage & Peripherals Industry - Apple', 'ORG')]",0.238452,positive,20250815T150059,low
"White House Reportedly Launches A Scorecard Rating 500+ Companies On Trump Loyalty - Who's Listed And How Ratings Are Determined - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Cisco Systems  ( NASDAQ:CSCO ) ","The White House has reportedly created a rating system to evaluate the support of corporate America for President Donald Trump's ""One Big Beautiful Bill"" and other policies. The White House has developed a scorecard evaluating 553 companies and trade associations on their support for the ""One Big ...",[],[],"[('White House', 'ORG'), ('Trump Loyalty -', 'PERSON'), ('Cisco Systems', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('The White House', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('The White House', 'ORG')]",0.371473,positive,20250815T133521,low
"How To Trade SPY And Top Tech Stocks Using Technical Analysis - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOGL ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Today's economic calendar wraps up the week on Friday, August 15, 2025, with a robust set of releases that could spark early market shifts.",[],[],"[('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.139359,positive,20250815T132014,low
AAPL FRAUD REMINDER: Apple Inc. Stock Drop Triggers Securities Fraud Class Action - Contact BFA Law before Imminent August 19 Deadline  ( NASDAQ:AAPL )  - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ,"NEW YORK, Aug. 15, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces that a lawsuit has been filed against Apple Inc. AAPL and certain of the Company's senior executives for potential violations of the federal securities laws.",[],[],"[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Company', 'ORG')]",0.1455,positive,20250815T121800,low
2 Dividend Stocks to Buy and Hold,These stocks look like they can weather almost any storm.,[],[],"[('Buy', 'PERSON')]",0.292414,positive,20250815T121500,low
Which High-Conviction Stock Picks Are Set to Soar in the Coming Years? Amazon  ( AMZN )  Is One.,These companies all have great long-term growth potential.,"[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('High-Conviction Stock Picks Are Set to Soar', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]",0.172673,positive,20250815T103000,low
Should Goldman Sachs ActiveBeta U.S. Large Cap Equity ETF  ( GSLC )  Be on Your Investing Radar?,Style Box ETF report for ...,[],[],"[('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('Style Box', 'PERSON')]",0.198247,positive,20250815T102002,low
2 Warren Buffett Stocks to Buy Hand Over Fist and 1 to Avoid,The Oracle of Omaha's investing strategies have stood the test of time.,[],[],"[('Warren Buffett Stocks', 'PERSON'), ('Buy Hand Over Fist', 'ORG'), ('Avoid The Oracle', 'ORG')]",0.215703,positive,20250815T101000,low
OpenAI CEO Sam Altman Reveals 'Sci-Fi' AI Companion Vision With Ex-Apple Design Chief Jony Ive To Replace Smartphones - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ,"OpenAI CEO Sam Altman detailed his vision for an artificial intelligence companion device during a recent podcast appearance, describing plans for ""ambiently aware"" hardware that could fundamentally change how users interact with technology beyond traditional smartphones.",[],[],"[('OpenAI', 'ORG'), ('Sam Altman', 'PERSON'), (""Sci-Fi'"", 'ORG'), ('OpenAI', 'ORG'), ('Sam Altman', 'PERSON')]",0.201703,positive,20250815T100357,low
3 Things Apple Investors Should Know Following a Recent Trump Announcement,CEO Tim Cook took part in a White House press event to tout Apple's investments in its domestic manufacturing footprint.,[],[],"[('Tim Cook', 'PERSON'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.165753,positive,20250815T095500,low
Should You Buy Berkshire Hathaway Stock While It's Under $500? Warren Buffett Gives Investors a Clear Answer.,"Investors can confidently buy Berkshire stock whenever Warren Buffett repurchases shares, but the buybacks stopped four quarters ago.",[],[],"[('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON')]",0.154569,positive,20250815T080500,low
"Dan Ives Says Apple's AI Strategy Has Been A 'Disaster' And No One On The Street Believes Innovation Will Come From Within - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOG ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","On Thursday, Wedbush analyst Dan Ives called Tim Cook-led Apple Inc.'s AAPL artificial intelligence strategy a ""disaster"" as he once again reiterated that the tech giant is lagging far behind competitors like Meta Platforms, Inc. META, Microsoft Corporation MSFT and startups like OpenAI.",[],[],"[('Dan Ives', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Wedbush', 'ORG'), ('Dan Ives', 'PERSON'), ('Tim Cook-led', 'PERSON'), (""Apple Inc.'s"", 'ORG'), ('Meta Platforms, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft Corporation', 'ORG')]",0.103912,positive,20250815T052808,low
"UnitedHealth Surges 11% As Michael Burry's Options Play, Warren Buffett's New Stake Signal Bold Rebound Bet - T-Mobile US  ( NASDAQ:TMUS ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ",UnitedHealth Group Inc. UNH is trending after the stock surged 10.69% in after-hours trading on Thursday following disclosure that legendary investors Michael Burry and Warren Buffett have taken significant positions in the healthcare giant. Check out the current price of UNH stock here.,[],[],"[('UnitedHealth Surges', 'ORG'), ('Michael Burry', 'PERSON'), (""Warren Buffett's"", 'PERSON'), ('New Stake Signal Bold Rebound Bet - T-Mobile US', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth Group Inc.', 'ORG'), ('UNH', 'ORG'), ('Michael Burry', 'PERSON'), ('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('UNH', 'ORG')]",0.20271,positive,20250815T042153,low
"Buffett Reveals UnitedHealth Stake, Trims Apple In Berkshire Hathaway Q2 13F Filing - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Allegion  ( NYSE:ALLE ) ","Warren Buffett unveiled several new stock positions for Berkshire Hathaway in the second quarter. UnitedHealth is a new position for Berkshire Hathaway. See what Wall Street is buying with instant access to ratings on 1,000 top stocks, including Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, and more.",[],[],"[('Buffett Reveals UnitedHealth Stake', 'ORG'), ('Filing - Apple', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('ALLE', 'ORG'), ('Warren Buffett', 'PERSON'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('UnitedHealth', 'ORG'), ('Berkshire Hathaway', 'PERSON'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('Morgan Stanley', 'ORG')]",0.221736,positive,20250814T205101,low
"Apple Inc. Investors: Please contact the Portnoy Law Firm to recover your losses. August 19, 2025 Deadline to file Lead Plaintiff Motion - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Investors can contact the law firm at no cost to learn more about recovering their losses LOS ANGELES, Aug. 14, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- The Portnoy Law Firm advises Apple Inc. ( ""Apple"" or the ""Company"" ) AAPL investors of a class action representing investors that bought securities between ...",[],[],"[('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Lead Plaintiff Motion - Apple', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.049053,positive,20250814T195944,low
"Arm Holdings Shares Up 15% in 2025: Is it Time to Buy, Hold, or Sell?","China headwinds, CPU venture risks, and a steep valuation premium temper Arm Holdings' AI and IoT momentum.",[],[],"[('Sell', 'PERSON'), ('CPU', 'ORG'), ('IoT', 'ORG')]",0.113717,positive,20250814T170600,low
What's Going On With Apple Stock Thursday? - Masimo  ( NASDAQ:MASI ) ,"U.S. update restores Blood Oxygen to Apple Watch Series 9, Series 10, and Ultra 2. Masimo shares fall 3.4% as Apple reintroduces the disputed feature. See what Wall Street is buying with instant access to ratings on 1,000 top stocks, including Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, and more.",[],[],"[('Masimo', 'PERSON'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('MASI', 'ORG'), ('Blood Oxygen to', 'ORG'), ('Apple Watch Series', 'ORG'), ('Masimo', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG'), ('Morgan Stanley', 'ORG')]",0.035812,positive,20250814T165013,low
4 Women-Run Company Stocks Showing Strong 2025 Gains,These women-run company stocks offer high growth and stability.,"[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('Women-Run Company Stocks', 'ORG')]",0.413532,positive,20250814T163500,low
Nokia and MX Fiber Expand Gigabit Connectivity Across Southeast Mexico,"NOK deploys a 1,800 km high-speed optical network for MX Fiber, boosting digital access and economic growth in Southeast Mexico.","[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('Nokia', 'ORG'), ('MX Fiber Expand Gigabit Connectivity Across Southeast Mexico NOK', 'ORG')]",0.388957,positive,20250814T155300,low
"What's Going On With Semiconductor Stocks Today - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Advanced Micro Devices  ( NASDAQ:AMD ) ","Chip stocks trend as profit-taking meets massive AI spending plans, led by $250B+ investments from Meta, Microsoft, and Google. Wedbush says Trump's China AI chip deal boosts Nvidia, AMD, and Big Tech, removing a key growth barrier for the next 12-18 months.","[('profit', 'positive'), ('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('Advanced Micro Devices', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('AMD', 'ORG'), ('Meta', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Wedbush', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('AMD', 'ORG')]",0.257548,positive,20250814T150812,low
"Inquiry Into Apple's Competitor Dynamics In Technology Hardware, Storage & Peripherals Industry - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","In the ever-changing and fiercely competitive business landscape, conducting thorough company analysis is crucial for investors and industry experts. In this article, we will undertake a comprehensive industry comparison, evaluating Apple AAPL and its primary competitors in the Technology ...",[],[],"[(""Inquiry Into Apple's"", 'ORG'), ('Storage & Peripherals Industry - Apple', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",0.230916,positive,20250814T150053,low
