title,summary,keywords,phrases,entities,sentiment,sentiment_label,time_published,risk_factor
"Larry Ellison Once Said Bill Gates Isn't The Smartest Or Most 'Brilliant,' But Has Two Traits That Very Few Have-'Bill, Forgive Me' - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , IBM  ( NYSE:IBM ) ","Larry Ellison lauded Billionaire Bill Gates for his exceptional business acumen, calling him one of the most remarkable business people he has ever met. Ellison, the co-founder of Oracle Corporation ORCL in a 2011 interview with TellTaleStory stated, ""There are a lot of brilliant, really ...",[],[],"[('Larry Ellison Once', 'PERSON'), ('Bill Gates', 'PERSON'), (""Forgive Me' - Microsoft"", 'ORG'), ('IBM', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('IBM', 'ORG'), ('Larry Ellison', 'PERSON'), ('Ellison', 'PERSON'), ('Oracle Corporation', 'ORG')]",0.464323,positive,20250819T124944,low
"Market Clubhouse Morning Memo - August 19th, 2025  ( Trade Strategy For SPY, QQQ, AAPL, MSFT, NVDA, GOOGL, META and TSLA )  - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOGL ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Good Morning Traders! In today's Market Clubhouse Morning Memo, we will discuss SPY, QQQ, AAPL, MSFT, NVDA, GOOGL, META, and TSLA. Our proprietary formula, exclusive to Market Clubhouse, dictates these price levels. This dynamic equation takes into account price, volume, and options flow.",[],[],"[('SPY', 'ORG'), ('QQQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('GOOGL', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('SPY', 'ORG'), ('QQQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('GOOGL', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Market Clubhouse', 'PERSON')]",0.117486,positive,20250819T124052,low
New PXM Manifesto Demonstrates Urgency of Leading in the Age of Agentic AI,"BOSTON, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Salsify, the leading Product Experience Management ( PXM ) platform, today announced the publication of ""The PXM AI Manifesto,"" a no-nonsense guide for digital commerce leaders.",[],[],"[('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Salsify', 'ORG'), ('Product Experience Management', 'ORG'), ('PXM', 'ORG')]",0.220868,positive,20250819T120500,low
Immutable and Koin Games Launch Project O: World's first competitive TCG for mobile,"SYDNEY, Aug. 19, 2025 /PRNewswire/ -- Immutable and Koin Games today unveiled Project O, a groundbreaking competitive trading card game ( TCG ) built natively for mobile.",[],[],"[('Project O', 'ORG')]",0.318306,positive,20250819T120000,low
Why Is Nvidia Stock Gaining Tuesday? - NVIDIA  ( NASDAQ:NVDA ) ,"Nvidia readies Blackwell-based B30A and RTX6000D chips for China to skirt U.S. curbs and defend its 13% revenue share. Analysts split: Bernstein sees shrinking China share, while Needham projects $20B sales by 2028 on Blackwell demand.",[],[],"[('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('Blackwell', 'PERSON'), ('B30A', 'ORG'), ('Bernstein', 'PERSON'), ('Needham', 'ORG'), ('Blackwell', 'PERSON')]",0.087614,positive,20250819T111245,low
Should SPDR Dow Jones Industrial Average ETF  ( DIA )  Be on Your Investing Radar?,Style Box ETF report for DIA ...,[],[],"[('DIA', 'ORG'), ('Style Box', 'PERSON'), ('DIA', 'ORG')]",0.244468,positive,20250819T102002,low
"The Best Stocks to Invest $1,000 in Right Now",There are still some good deals available for long-term investors.,[],[],"[('Invest', 'ORG')]",0.279164,positive,20250819T093500,low
"Billionaires Buy a Brilliant Vanguard Index Fund That Could Turn $500 Per Month Into $442,400 With Help From the ""Magnificent Seven"" Stocks","This Vanguard index fund is heavily invested in the ""Magnificent Seven"" stocks, a group that includes Nvidia, Microsoft, Apple, Amazon, Meta Platforms, Alphabet, and Tesla.",[],[],"[('Vanguard', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('Alphabet', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'ORG')]",0.423341,positive,20250819T080400,low
"This Formerly High-Flying Cryptocurrency Has the Potential to Become the New Bitcoin, According to Tom Lee of Fundstrat",Tom Lee of Fundstrat sees Ethereum as a cryptocurrency with Bitcoin-style potential.,[],[],"[('Tom Lee', 'PERSON'), ('Tom Lee', 'PERSON'), ('Ethereum', 'PERSON')]",0.314673,positive,20250819T080000,low
"Deepwater's Doug Clinton Says Apple, Amazon's AI Stories Are Weak: From Nvidia To Meta, Here's What His AI Models Are A Fan Of - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) ","Doug Clinton, CEO of Intelligent Alpha and Co-founder of Deepwater Asset Management, believes Apple Inc. AAPL and Amazon.com Inc. AMZN are lagging in the artificial intelligence race compared to their tech giant peers. ArrivedBuy shares of homes and vacation rentals for as little as $100.",[],[],"[(""Deepwater's"", 'ORG'), ('Doug Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('AI Stories Are Weak:', 'ORG'), ('Amazon.com', 'ORG'), ('Doug Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Intelligent Alpha and Co-', 'ORG'), ('Deepwater Asset Management', 'ORG'), ('Apple Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Amazon.com Inc.', 'ORG'), ('ArrivedBuy', 'ORG')]",0.179084,positive,20250819T075139,low
"OpenAI bets on cheapest ChatGPT plan at $4.6, starting in India","OpenAI has launched a subscription plan for users in India, priced at just 399 rupees ($4.57) per month, its most affordable offering yet.",[],[],"[('OpenAI', 'ORG')]",0.111369,positive,20250819T063007,low
"MSNBC Drops Iconic Peacock Logo, Will Rebrand As 'MS Now' As Network Splits From NBC News - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Comcast  ( NASDAQ:CMCSA ) ","MSNBC Drops Iconic Name After Nearly 30 Years, Will Become MS Now As Network Splits From NBC News MSNBC will shed its longtime brand later this year and reintroduce itself as MS Now as the network separates from NBC News and asserts a more independent identity.",[],[],"[('MSNBC Drops', 'ORG'), ('Will Rebrand', 'PERSON'), ('NBC News - Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Comcast', 'ORG'), ('MSNBC Drops Iconic Name', 'ORG'), ('Will Become MS Now', 'ORG'), ('NBC News', 'ORG'), ('MSNBC', 'ORG'), ('MS Now', 'ORG'), ('NBC News', 'ORG')]",0.116846,positive,20250819T061920,low
Navatar Unveils AI-Powered CRM That Meets M&A Advisors Where They Work From Outlook to Slack to CRM: Investment Banking's First Truly Embedded Intelligence Platform For Salesforce,"LONDON and NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Navatar, the leading platform for private markets, today announced the launch of its next-generation, fully AI-powered CRM purpose-built for M&A advisory firms.",[],[],"[('Navatar Unveils AI-Powered CRM That Meets M&A Advisors Where They Work From Outlook to Slack', 'ORG'), (""Investment Banking's"", 'ORG'), ('First Truly Embedded Intelligence Platform For Salesforce LONDON', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG')]",0.180813,positive,20250819T052800,low
Predicting the Next Rule Breaker Buyout,"Having a stock you own get acquired at a premium feels good at first, but what about the long-term gains that will be left behind when your chips are off the table?",[],[],"[('the Next Rule Breaker Buyout Having', 'ORG')]",0.170253,positive,20250819T040800,low
"Preface launches ""Just Start"" AI learning initiative: Hong Kong's first AI-Q Test debuts, with over 30 organisations including Google, Microsoft and Meta joining forces to promote AI for all","[The content of this article has been produced by our advertising partner.] In an era where artificial intelligence defines competitive advantage, Hong Kong faces a critical choice: adapt collectively or risk obsolescence.",[],[],"[('AI-Q Test', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Meta', 'ORG')]",0.218927,positive,20250819T035908,low
"Allianz Life Hack Reportedly Exposes 1.1 Million Customers As US Cyberattack Wave Escalates With Microsoft And UnitedHealth Breaches - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , UnitedHealth Group  ( NYSE:UNH ) ","A cyberattack on Allianz Life has reportedly exposed the personal data of 1.1 million people, adding to a string of high-profile breaches impacting U.S. companies, including Microsoft Corporation MSFT and UnitedHealth Group Inc. UNH.",[],[],"[('Allianz Life Hack Reportedly', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth Breaches - Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth Group', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('UNH', 'ORG'), ('Allianz Life', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft Corporation', 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth Group Inc.', 'ORG'), ('UNH', 'ORG')]",-0.329927,negative,20250819T035054,low
Should You Buy Nvidia Stock Before Aug. 27? Here's What History Suggests.,Nvidia stock is scheduled to report second-quarter earnings on Aug. 27.,[],[],"[('Nvidia', 'ORG')]",0.186948,positive,20250819T010000,low
Asia-Pacific markets mostly fall as investors assess outcome of Trump-Zelenskyy meeting,"Investors are also looking ahead to the U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's annual speech at the central bank's summit in Jackson Hole, Wyoming.",[],[],"[('Trump-Zelenskyy meeting Investors', 'ORG'), ('the U.S. Federal Reserve', 'ORG'), ('Jerome Powell', 'PERSON'), (""the central bank's"", 'ORG')]",-0.01658,negative,20250819T001743,low
Graphjet to collaborate with Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia for the development of thermal management material using graphite,"New York, United States, Aug. 18, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Graphjet Technology ( ""Graphjet"" or ""the Company"" ) has agreed to support and collaborate with Centre for Materials Engineering and Smart Manufacturing ( MERCU ) of Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia ( UKM ) after receiving a letter of ...",[],[],"[('Universiti', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Graphjet Technology', 'ORG'), ('Centre for Materials Engineering', 'ORG'), ('Smart Manufacturing', 'ORG'), ('MERCU', 'ORG'), ('Universiti', 'ORG'), ('UKM', 'ORG')]",0.153321,positive,20250818T203000,low
Autonomous Vehicles Hit an Inflection Point; GPT-5 Is Here,Motley Fool Money checks in on some stock market news.,[],[],[],0.130658,positive,20250818T202200,low
"AI, Quantum, and the Future of Tech Investing",Here's how you can invest in the next wave of innovation.,[],[],"[('Quantum', 'ORG'), (""the Future of Tech Investing Here's"", 'ORG')]",0.088146,positive,20250818T192000,low
How Ethereum Treasury Companies are Following the BTC Playbook,"Crypto treasury companies are evolving beyond Bitcoin. While pioneers like MicroStrategy showed the world what was possible, companies like Bitmine Immersion are now taking that playbook and applying it to Ethereum.",[],[],"[('MicroStrategy', 'ORG'), ('Bitmine Immersion', 'ORG'), ('Ethereum', 'ORG')]",0.290912,positive,20250818T180900,low
How Hackers Are Using Fake Captchas to Spread Lumma Stealer Malware,"The malware scours infected devices for sensitive information including passwords, 2FA tokens and crypto wallet data.",[],[],[],-0.166986,negative,20250818T174822,low
SentinelOne's Singularity Platform Fuels Revenue: Will It Sustain?,"S's AI-powered Singularity platform is driving strong revenue and ARR growth, but stiff competition looms.","[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('SentinelOne', 'ORG'), ('ARR', 'ORG')]",0.279655,positive,20250818T172200,low
Shopify Benefits From Growing Merchant Base: Should You Buy or Wait?,"SHOP's surging merchant revenues, global expansion, and AI-powered tools drive momentum, but valuation and competition raise caution.","[('expansion', 'positive')]",[],[],0.303422,positive,20250818T171800,low
Hackers Using Fake Captchas to Spread Lumma Stealer Malware,"The malware scours infected devices for sensitive information including passwords, 2FA tokens and crypto wallet data.",[],[],"[('Hackers Using Fake Captchas', 'ORG')]",-0.164412,negative,20250818T165633,low
Oracle Strengthens GenAI Push: Will Google Cloud Tie-Up Pay Off?,"ORCL deepens its GenAI push with Google Cloud, embedding Gemini into OCI and apps to drive enterprise adoption and growth.","[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('Oracle Strengthens', 'PERSON'), ('Google Cloud', 'PERSON')]",0.256941,positive,20250818T163600,low
"AI Science To Soul... Blind Visionary & Paradigm Disruptor Sean Callagy, ACTi, & Unblinded Plant The Flag In New Reality, Launching Visioneer Ecosystem & Answering All","Paramus, NJ August 18, 2025 -- ( PR.com ) -- Since the dawn of humanity, every human being, regardless of culture or period, from the ancient Greeks to the Founding Fathers of America to every human being on earth in August of 2025, has wrestled with two questions: ""Why am I here?"" and ""How do I ...",[],[],"[('Blind Visionary & Paradigm', 'ORG'), ('Sean Callagy', 'PERSON'), ('Visioneer Ecosystem & Answering All', 'ORG'), ('NJ', 'ORG'), ('PR.com', 'ORG'), ('Greeks', 'PERSON')]",0.298214,positive,20250818T162634,low
"Okta Plunges 27% in 3 Months: Buy, Sell or Hold the Stock?","OKTA's shares slump amid federal business slowdown and macro headwinds, but its expanding portfolio and partner base signal long-term strength.",[],[],"[('Okta Plunges 27%', 'ORG'), ('Sell', 'PERSON')]",0.263931,positive,20250818T161200,low
Can ServiceNow's Expanding AI-Powered Platform Drive the Stock Higher?,"NOW grows AI-driven revenues with NVIDIA and Logik.ai support, but execution risks and valuation spark caution.",[],[],"[('ServiceNow', 'ORG'), ('Expanding AI-Powered Platform Drive the Stock Higher', 'ORG')]",0.219822,positive,20250818T160500,low
Microsoft's Azure Boom Lifts Cloud Revenues: More Upside Ahead?,"MSFT's cloud revenues hit $46.7B in Q4 as Azure rose 39%, with annual revenues topping $75B for the first time.",[],[],"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Azure Boom Lifts Cloud Revenues', 'ORG'), ('MSFT', 'ORG')]",0.198819,positive,20250818T155400,low
AppLovin Stock Skyrockets 20% in a Month: Should You Board the Train?,"APP's Axon 2 fuels ad spend surge, revenue jumps 77%, and profits soar, driving a 20% stock rally with bullish growth forecasts.","[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('AppLovin Stock Skyrockets', 'ORG'), ('APP', 'ORG'), ('Axon 2', 'PERSON')]",0.374257,positive,20250818T154600,low
"Should You Buy, Sell or Hold CyberArk Stock After a 27.2% YTD Rise?",CYBR is benefiting from growth fueled by AI-driven identity security growth and major partnerships.,"[('growth', 'positive'), ('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('Hold CyberArk Stock', 'ORG')]",0.397087,positive,20250818T150100,low
In-Depth Analysis: Microsoft Versus Competitors In Software Industry - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) ,"In the dynamic and cutthroat world of business, conducting thorough company analysis is essential for investors and industry experts. In this article, we will undertake a comprehensive industry comparison, evaluating Microsoft MSFT and its primary competitors in the Software industry.",[],[],"[('Microsoft Versus Competitors', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft MSFT', 'ORG'), ('Software', 'ORG')]",0.222114,positive,20250818T150024,low
QUBT Expands Verticals From Aerospace to Cybersecurity: Stock to Gain?,"QUBT's technology is gaining traction across aerospace, automotive and cybersecurity, fueling adoption despite financial hurdles.",[],[],"[('QUBT Expands Verticals From Aerospace', 'ORG'), ('Cybersecurity: Stock', 'ORG'), ('QUBT', 'ORG')]",0.197033,positive,20250818T145900,low
IBM Gains 23% in a Year: Should You Bet on the Stock Now?,"IBM's 23% rally rides on hybrid cloud and AI momentum, with watsonx and NVIDIA partnerships fueling growth prospects.","[('growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('IBM', 'ORG'), ('IBM', 'ORG')]",0.386678,positive,20250818T143100,low
What's Going On With Oracle Stock Monday? - Oracle  ( NYSE:ORCL ) ,"Oracle embeds GPT-5 into databases and SaaS apps to boost automation, accuracy, and business insights. GPT-5 powers coding, debugging, and reasoning in Oracle workflows, streamlining processes and recommendations.",[],[],"[('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('ORCL', 'ORG')]",0.227025,positive,20250818T142625,low
"How To Trade SPY And Top Tech Stocks Today - Meta Platforms  ( NASDAQ:META ) , Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ",Today's economic calendar launches the week with a modest set of releases that could set a cautious tone for trading. The New York Fed Services Business Activity for August will provide a snapshot of regional service sector performance.,[],[],"[('Today - Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'PERSON'), ('The New York Fed Services Business Activity', 'ORG')]",0.024744,positive,20250818T140200,low
"Workplace Safety Market is expected to generate a revenue of USD 44.39 Billion by 2031, Globally, at 13.50% CAGR: Verified Market Research®","Lewes, Delaware, Aug. 18, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- The Global Workplace Safety Market Size is projected to grow at a CAGR of 13.50% from 2024 to 2031, according to a new report published by Verified Market Research®.",[],[],"[('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Verified Market Research®', 'ORG')]",0.39753,positive,20250818T140000,low
Insights Into 13F Filings: ETFs to Invest in Like Billionaires,"Hedge funds invest in Microsoft, UnitedHealth and homebuilders. ETFs like MAGS, IHF and XHB let you invest like billionaires.",[],[],"[('Invest', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('UnitedHealth', 'ORG'), ('MAGS', 'ORG'), ('IHF', 'ORG'), ('XHB', 'ORG')]",0.287019,positive,20250818T140000,low
Microsoft Opens 'Urgent' Probe Over Claims Israeli Military Used Its Tech To Monitor Palestinians - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) ,"Microsoft Corporation MSFT has launched an ""urgent"" external investigation into allegations that its technology was used by Israel's military surveillance agency to facilitate mass surveillance of Palestinians.",[],[],"[(""Microsoft Opens 'Urgent' Probe Over Claims Israeli Military Used Its Tech"", 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft Corporation', 'ORG')]",-0.148252,negative,20250818T133738,low
"OpenAI, Other Tech Firms Bypass American Workers, Favor H-1B Candidates Through Discriminatory Job Postings: Report - Meta Platforms  ( NASDAQ:META ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Major tech companies have been accused of using local newspaper job ads to target immigrant workers for green cards, potentially bypassing H-1B laws. Companies with H-1B employees in the green card process are said to be running local newspaper ads to appeal to immigrant job seekers.",[],[],"[('Tech Firms Bypass American Workers', 'ORG'), ('Favor H-1B Candidates Through Discriminatory Job Postings', 'ORG'), ('Report - Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]",-0.016531,negative,20250818T133632,low
What Is One of the Best Quantum Computing Stocks to Buy Now?,"While the new players are getting most of the hype, one company has been working on quantum for quite some time.",[],[],[],0.306019,positive,20250818T132312,low
"Dan Ives Just Revealed Four Explosive New Picks Into His AI Revolution 30 List - And He Says These Companies Will Define Future Of AI - CrowdStrike Holdings  ( NASDAQ:CRWD ) , Adobe  ( NASDAQ:ADBE ) ","Prominent Wedbush analyst Dan Ives has updated the holdings of his ""AI Revolution 30"" list, the basis for his new ETF, by adding four new companies and removing three. In a post on X Monday, Ives announced the inclusion of cybersecurity leader CrowdStrike Holdings Inc. CRWD, gaming platform ...",[],[],"[('Dan Ives', 'PERSON'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('CRWD', 'ORG'), ('Adobe  ', 'PERSON'), ('Wedbush', 'ORG'), ('Dan Ives', 'PERSON'), ('Ives', 'ORG'), ('CrowdStrike Holdings Inc.', 'ORG'), ('CRWD', 'ORG')]",0.172556,positive,20250818T124557,low
Here's Why Nvidia Outperforms Out to 2028,Nvidia's multilayered moat makes its dominance effectively unbreakable through 2028.,[],[],"[('Nvidia', 'ORG')]",0.224116,positive,20250818T124500,low
Is Quantum Computing Inc. Stock a Buy After Earnings?,Quantum Computing has become a popular stock in the artificial intelligence (AI) landscape over the last year.,[],[],"[('Quantum Computing Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Quantum Computing', 'ORG')]",0.234893,positive,20250818T122600,low
"3 Vanguard ETFs to Buy With $2,000 and Hold Forever",You can make money in the market without picking individual stocks. These three funds make investing easy and charge very low management fees.,[],[],"[('Buy With', 'ORG')]",0.255337,positive,20250818T120000,low
2 High-Powered Growth Stocks to Buy This Week,"One's racing SpaceX to connect every smartphone on Earth, while the other's building the quantum computers that could revolutionize everything.","[('Growth', 'positive')]",[],"[('Buy This Week', 'ORG')]",0.084941,positive,20250818T103000,low
Should WisdomTree U.S. LargeCap Dividend ETF  ( DLN )  Be on Your Investing Radar?,Style Box ETF report for ...,[],[],"[('U.S. LargeCap', 'ORG'), ('DLN', 'ORG'), ('Style Box', 'PERSON')]",0.217464,positive,20250818T102002,low
Should Schwab Fundamental U.S. Large Company ETF  ( FNDX )  Be on Your Investing Radar?,Style Box ETF report for ...,[],[],"[('Schwab Fundamental', 'ORG'), ('Style Box', 'PERSON')]",0.221653,positive,20250818T102002,low
