title,summary,keywords,phrases,entities,sentiment,sentiment_label,time_published,risk_factor
Think It's Too Late to Buy Rivian? Here's the No. 1 Reason Why There's Still Time.,Rivian stock still trades at a discount to the competition.,[],[],[],0.341991,positive,20250820T144300,low
3 Serious Tesla Problems Investors Aren't Talking Enough About,"While there are plenty of negative developments to choose from, Tesla investors need to remember these three.",[],[],"[('Serious Tesla Problems Investors', 'ORG')]",-0.149046,negative,20250820T113800,medium
What's Going On With Taiwan Semiconductor Stock Wednesday? - Taiwan Semiconductor  ( NYSE:TSM ) ,"TSMC's Arizona arm turned profitable in 2025, highlighting its strength as Samsung and Intel push harder to challenge its lead. Despite rivals' moves, TSMC expands aggressively with new fabs and advanced nodes to protect its dominance in global chipmaking.",[],[],"[('Taiwan Semiconductor Stock', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('TSMC', 'ORG'), ('Samsung', 'ORG'), ('Intel', 'ORG'), ('TSMC', 'ORG')]",0.280692,positive,20250820T111804,low
DIFD AUTO Reveals a New Era of Crypto-Powered Automotive Business,"LONDON, UK, Aug. 20, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- DIFD AUTO, a pioneering force in the automotive industry, has taken bold steps to redefine luxury and electric vehicle ( EV ) ownership with three groundbreaking announcements.",[],[],"[('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('EV', 'ORG')]",0.483391,positive,20250820T085219,low
Elon Musk Shelves 'America Party' Plans To Protect Ties With MAGA Movement: Report - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ,"Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla Inc. TSLA, has reportedly decided to halt his plans to establish a political party, amid hesitation to alienate influential Republicans. Musk has informed his associates about his intention to shift his focus back to his companies, The Wall Street Journal reported.",[],[],"[(""Elon Musk Shelves '"", 'PERSON'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla Inc.', 'ORG'), ('The Wall Street Journal', 'ORG')]",0.272092,positive,20250820T072802,low
"Here's Why You Will Still See SUVs From This Dead Tesla Rival On NYC Streets - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOG ) , Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOGL ) ","A fleet company in New York City, American Lease, has bought over unsold 2,800 units of the now-defunct Tesla Inc. TSLA rival Fisker's Ocean SUVs to operate as cabs in the city.",[],[],"[('Alphabet  (', 'PERSON'), ('American Lease', 'ORG'), ('Tesla Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Fisker', 'ORG')]",0.116539,positive,20250820T072424,low
"Chinese EV sector's global push, BYD takes on Tesla in Hong Kong: 7 EV reads","We have put together stories from our coverage on electric and new energy vehicles from the past two weeks to help you stay informed. If you would like to see more of our reporting, please consider subscribing. 1. Can China forge an offshore economic empire?",[],[],"[('BYD', 'ORG'), ('EV', 'ORG')]",0.014645,positive,20250820T070103,low
"US Increases Steel, Aluminum Tariffs On Over 400 Products Including EV Parts, Wind Turbines, Railcars - Ford Motor  ( NYSE:F ) , Cleveland-Cliffs  ( NYSE:CLF ) ","The U.S. Commerce Department has announced a significant increase in tariffs on steel and aluminum for over 400 products, including wind turbines, railcars, and electric vehicle ( EV ) parts. ArrivedBuy shares of homes and vacation rentals for as little as $100. Get Started",[],[],"[('US Increases Steel', 'ORG'), ('Railcars - Ford Motor', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('The U.S. Commerce Department', 'ORG'), ('EV', 'ORG'), ('ArrivedBuy', 'ORG')]",0.124523,positive,20250820T065448,low
Elon Musk's 'America Party' plans have stalled: Report,"Elon Musk will reportedly back Vice President JD Vance in the 2028 presidential elections should he choose to run, The Wall Street Journal reports.",[],[],"[(""Elon Musk's '"", 'PERSON'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('JD Vance', 'PERSON'), ('The Wall Street Journal', 'ORG')]",0.302606,positive,20250820T064910,low
Tesla Begins Testing FSD In This Asian Country While Facing Lawsuits Back Home - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ,"Tesla Inc. TSLA has begun testing its FSD or Full Self-Driving system in countries outside the U.S. amid the fiercely competitive autonomous driving race. Elon Musk's EV giant has begun conducting testing in Japan, according to a post shared on the social media platform X from Tesla Japan's ...",[],[],"[('This Asian Country While Facing Lawsuits Back Home - Tesla', 'ORG'), ('Tesla Inc.', 'ORG'), ('FSD', 'ORG'), ('Full Self-Driving', 'PERSON'), (""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON'), ('EV', 'ORG'), (""Tesla Japan's"", 'ORG')]",-0.041131,negative,20250820T055101,medium
Elon Musk's Tesla Loses Bid To Dismiss Class Action Lawsuit Over Misleading FSD Claims - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ,Tesla Inc. TSLA has lost a bid to dismiss a proposed class action lawsuit against the automaker over its misleading claims about the FSD or Full Self-Driving system.,[],[],"[(""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON'), ('Tesla Inc.', 'ORG'), ('FSD', 'ORG'), ('Full Self-Driving', 'PERSON')]",-0.103667,negative,20250820T041441,medium
Amber International Is First Asian Listed Firm To Launch On-Chain Shares Under AMBRx Symbol - Amber International  ( NASDAQ:AMBR ) ,"Amber International Holding Ltd. AMBR has become the first Asia-based public company to offer its stock on-chain, trading as AMBRx on the solana blockchain, CEO Wayne Huo confirmed on Tuesday during a live webinar hosted on Futubull by Futu.",[],[],"[('Symbol - Amber International', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('AMBR', 'PERSON'), ('Amber International Holding Ltd.', 'ORG'), ('Wayne Huo', 'PERSON'), ('Futubull', 'PERSON')]",0.177694,positive,20250819T221754,low
"Why We Believe The US Mulling A 10% Stake In Intel Is Negative - Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) , SoftBank Group  ( OTC:SFTBY ) ","To gain an edge, this is what you need to know today. This article is about the big picture, not an individual stock. The chart of HD stock is being used to illustrate the point. Home Depot is important because it is the largest retailer of home improvement goods in the country.",[],[],"[('Intel', 'ORG'), ('SoftBank Group', 'ORG'), ('Home Depot', 'ORG')]",0.30127,positive,20250819T213614,low
"From Elevated To Worrisome - Gravity Always Wins, Billionaire Investor Says - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) ","Marks warns S&P gains are dangerously concentrated, with 58% of returns tied to the Magnificent Seven. He places markets at INVESTCON 5: time to cut aggressive bets and lean defensive. See what Wall Street is buying with instant access to ratings on 1,000 top stocks, including Goldman Sachs, ...",[],[],"[('Worrisome - Gravity Always Wins', 'ORG'), ('Amazon.com', 'ORG'), ('Marks', 'ORG'), ('S&P', 'ORG'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'ORG')]",0.170814,positive,20250819T175644,low
Strategy Falls 15% in a Month: Hold or Fold the MSTR Stock?,Strategy's bitcoin gains and disciplined capital raising contrast with steep share declines and premium valuation concerns.,[],[],"[('Strategy Falls', 'PERSON')]",0.201064,positive,20250819T162300,low
Plug Power Stock Slides As Trump's EV Credit Rollback And Weak Demand Shake The Industry - Plug Power  ( NASDAQ:PLUG ) ,"Plug Power sinks 25% YTD as analysts flag cash burn, margin risks despite stronger Q2 revenue. EV demand weakens in U.S. after Trump ends $7,500 credit; automakers slash prices, scale back plans. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise into opportunity.",[],[],"[('Plug Power Stock Slides', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Plug Power', 'ORG'), ('EV', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]",-0.054298,negative,20250819T161639,medium
"Antidote To AI Bubble Call By OpenAI CEO Altman, Google Gives Big Boost To Nuclear Power - NVIDIA  ( NASDAQ:NVDA ) , SPDR Gold Trust  ( ARCA:GLD ) ","To gain an edge, this is what you need to know today. Please click here for an enlarged chart of NVIDIA Corp NVDA. We have previously shared with readers that we expects AI to follow the change curve.",[],[],"[('OpenAI', 'PERSON'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('SPDR Gold Trust', 'ORG'), ('NVIDIA Corp NVDA', 'ORG')]",0.28397,positive,20250819T153050,low
Stevens Capital Significantly Cuts its Tesla Position,"Stevens Capital Management LP reported in a regulatory filing dated Aug. 12, 2025, that it sold 89,187 shares of Tesla ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) during the second quarter of 2025. The estimated transaction value was $26.81 million, based on the average price of tesla shares in the second quarter.",[],"[('sold', 'medium_risk')]","[('Stevens Capital Significantly Cuts', 'ORG'), ('Stevens Capital Management LP', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG')]",0.279221,positive,20250819T144314,medium
Why Tesla Cybertruck sales are falling short of expectations,"Tesla said Cybertruck demand was ""off the charts"". Sales never met expectations, and have been falling. But some owners love their trucks. So, what happened?",[],[],"[('Tesla Cybertruck', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('Cybertruck', 'PERSON')]",0.175866,positive,20250819T142756,low
KindlyMD Expands Bitcoin Treasury With $679 Million Acquisition - Kindly MD  ( NASDAQ:NAKA ) ,"KindlyMD merged with Nakamoto Holdings this month, combining healthcare services with a Bitcoin-focused institutional treasury strategy. The acquisition underscores growing corporate recognition of Bitcoin as a financial anchor in the shifting global economy.",[],[],"[('KindlyMD Expands Bitcoin Treasury', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('NAKA', 'ORG'), ('KindlyMD', 'PERSON'), ('Nakamoto Holdings', 'ORG'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON')]",0.202947,positive,20250819T142340,low
"Tesla's 10X P/S Premium: Is the Stock a Buy, Hold or Sell Now?","TSLA's steep sales decline, shrinking margins and intensifying competition cast doubt on its lofty 10X sales premium.","[('decline', 'negative')]",[],"[('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('P/S Premium: Is the Stock a Buy', 'ORG')]",0.070441,positive,20250819T131200,medium
"Here is What to Know Beyond Why Tesla, Inc.  ( TSLA )  is a Trending Stock","Tesla (TSLA) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Therefore, it is wise to be aware of the facts that can impact the stock's prospects.",[],[],"[('Zacks.com', 'ORG')]",0.235063,positive,20250819T130003,low
Why Is Nio Stock Climbing Tuesday? - NIO  ( NYSE:NIO ) ,"Nio cuts 100-kWh battery pack price by 20,000 Chinese yuan. Nio plans market entries in Singapore, Uzbekistan, and Costa Rica. Get the exact trades and sectors to target before August's biggest earnings-driven market moves. Details here → Nio Inc.",[],[],"[('NYSE', 'ORG')]",0.111131,positive,20250819T125255,low
"Market Clubhouse Morning Memo - August 19th, 2025  ( Trade Strategy For SPY, QQQ, AAPL, MSFT, NVDA, GOOGL, META and TSLA )  - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOGL ) , Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) ","Good Morning Traders! In today's Market Clubhouse Morning Memo, we will discuss SPY, QQQ, AAPL, MSFT, NVDA, GOOGL, META, and TSLA. Our proprietary formula, exclusive to Market Clubhouse, dictates these price levels. This dynamic equation takes into account price, volume, and options flow.",[],[],"[('SPY', 'ORG'), ('QQQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('GOOGL', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('SPY', 'ORG'), ('QQQ', 'ORG'), ('NVDA', 'ORG'), ('GOOGL', 'ORG'), ('META', 'ORG'), ('Market Clubhouse', 'PERSON')]",0.117486,positive,20250819T124052,low
SJM SECURITIES: J.M. Smucker Co. Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law  ( NYSE:SJM )  - JM Smucker  ( NYSE:SJM ) ,"NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces an investigation into The J.M. Smucker Company SJM for potential violations of the federal securities laws. If you invested in J.M.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('J.M. Smucker Co. Shareholders', 'ORG'), ('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('The J.M. Smucker Company SJM', 'ORG')]",0.26811,positive,20250819T123800,medium
FLYW SECURITIES: Flywire Corporation Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law before the Class Action Deadline  ( NASDAQ:FLYW )  - Flywire  ( NASDAQ:FLYW ) ,"NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces that a lawsuit has been filed against Flywire Corporation FLYW and certain of the Company's senior executives for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('Flywire Corporation FLYW', 'ORG'), ('Company', 'ORG')]",0.134272,positive,20250819T123600,medium
"BRBR SECURITIES: BellRing Brands, Inc. Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law  ( NYSE:BRBR )  - BellRing Brands  ( NYSE:BRBR ) ","NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces an investigation into BellRing Brands, Inc. BRBR for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('BellRing Brands', 'ORG'), ('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('BellRing Brands', 'ORG')]",0.254956,positive,20250819T123600,medium
CNC SECURITIES: Centene Corporation Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law before the Class Action Deadline  ( NYSE:CNC )  - Centene  ( NYSE:CNC ) ,"NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces that a lawsuit has been filed against Centene Corporation CNC and certain of the Company's senior executives for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('Company', 'ORG')]",0.240049,positive,20250819T123600,medium
"SRPT SECURITIES: Sarepta Therapeutics, Inc. Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law before the Class Action Deadline  ( NASDAQ:SRPT )  - Sarepta Therapeutics  ( NASDAQ:SRPT ) ","NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces that a lawsuit has been filed against Sarepta Therapeutics, Inc. SRPT and certain of the Company's senior executives for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('Sarepta Therapeutics, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('Sarepta Therapeutics, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Company', 'ORG')]",0.104505,positive,20250819T123600,medium
"SLP SECURITIES: Simulations Plus, Inc. Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law  ( NASDAQ:SLP )  - Simulations Plus  ( NASDAQ:SLP ) ","NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces an investigation into Simulations Plus, Inc. SLP for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('Simulations Plus, Inc. SLP', 'ORG')]",0.2059,positive,20250819T123600,medium
"RXST SECURITIES: RxSight, Inc. Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law before the Class Action Deadline  ( NASDAQ:RXST )  - RxSight  ( NASDAQ:RXST ) ","NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces that a lawsuit has been filed against RxSight, Inc. RXST and certain of the Company's senior executives for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('RxSight, Inc. Shareholders', 'ORG'), ('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('RxSight, Inc. RXST', 'ORG'), ('Company', 'ORG')]",0.156722,positive,20250819T123500,medium
"LINE SECURITIES: Lineage, Inc. Shareholders that Lost Money may have been Affected by Fraud -- Contact BFA Law before the Class Action Deadline  ( NASDAQ:LINE )  - Lineage  ( NASDAQ:LINE ) ","NEW YORK, Aug. 19, 2025 ( GLOBE NEWSWIRE ) -- Leading securities law firm Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP announces that a lawsuit has been filed against Lineage, Inc. LINE and certain of the Company's senior executives and directors for potential violations of the federal securities laws.","[('Fraud', 'negative')]",[],"[('Lineage, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Lost Money', 'ORG'), ('GLOBE NEWSWIRE', 'ORG'), ('Bleichmar Fonti & Auld LLP', 'ORG'), ('Lineage, Inc. LINE', 'ORG'), ('Company', 'ORG')]",0.128581,positive,20250819T123300,medium
Can Tesla's New Model Y L Boost its Sales Volumes in China?,TSLA launches the six-seat Model Y L in China to regain ground as sales slip and competition from local players rises.,[],[],[],0.120665,positive,20250819T121700,low
What's Going On With XPeng Stock Tuesday? - XPeng  ( NYSE:XPEV ) ,"XPeng Q2 revenue jumped 125% Y/Y to $2.55B, topping estimates; deliveries surged 242% to 103,181 vehicles. Gross margin hit a record 17.3%; Q3 deliveries guided up 143%-154% Y/Y with revenue of $2.7B-$2.9B. Get the exact trades and sectors to target before August's biggest earnings-driven market ...",[],[],"[('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('XPeng Q2', 'PERSON')]",0.016687,positive,20250819T111025,low
Where Will Dogecoin Be in 5 Years?,"Dogecoin showed that meme coins can make serious money, but the next five years could be rocky.",[],[],[],0.223278,positive,20250819T104500,low
Tesla Records 14K New Insured Registrations In China From August 11 To 17 - 60% Surge Over Last Quarter - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ,"Tesla Inc. TSLA sales in China experienced a 4.5% surge for the week of August 11 to 17, as the automaker struggles with declining sales globally. The company recorded 14k new insured registrations in China, a 60% surge compared to the previous quarter for Tesla, data shared by influencer Roland ...",[],"[('declining sales', 'medium_risk')]","[('Tesla Records', 'ORG'), ('K New Insured Registrations In', 'ORG'), ('Tesla Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('Roland', 'PERSON')]",0.009516,positive,20250819T103302,medium
"The Best Stocks to Invest $1,000 in Right Now",There are still some good deals available for long-term investors.,[],[],"[('Invest', 'ORG')]",0.279164,positive,20250819T093500,low
"Marjorie Taylor Greene Faces Possible Ethics Probe, Penalties Over Omitted Book Deal Despite Six-Figure Royalties: Report - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) , Palantir Technologies  ( NASDAQ:PLTR ) ",The financial disclosure of Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene ( R-Ga. ) has reportedly come under scanner due to the omission of her book agreement.,"[('Probe', 'negative')]",[],"[('Marjorie Taylor', 'PERSON'), ('Palantir Technologies', 'ORG'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('PLTR', 'ORG'), ('Marjorie Taylor Greene', 'PERSON')]",0.151576,positive,20250819T090345,medium
"Tesla Insiders Have Unloaded More Than 50% Equity In Elon Musk's EV Giant Over The Last Year: Report - BYD  ( OTC:BYDDF ) , BYD  ( OTC:BYDDY ) ","Tesla Inc. TSLA insiders, including members of the board of directors, have reportedly sold more than 50% equity in the company. ArrivedBuy shares of homes and vacation rentals for as little as $100. Get Started Interactive BrokersTrade global markets with low costs and pro-level tools at ...",[],"[('sold', 'medium_risk')]","[('BYD', 'ORG'), ('BYDDY', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla Inc.', 'ORG'), ('ArrivedBuy', 'ORG')]",0.115651,positive,20250819T081617,medium
Alphabet's Waymo Tests New Robotaxi With 6th-Gen Autonomous Hardware As Self-Driving Race Heats Up - Alphabet  ( NASDAQ:GOOGL ) ,Alphabet Inc.'s GOOGL GOOG autonomous ride-hailing company Waymo has begun testing its new Robotaxi with sixth-generation self-driving hardware.,[],[],"[(""Alphabet's"", 'ORG'), ('Waymo Tests New Robotaxi', 'ORG'), (""Alphabet Inc.'s"", 'ORG'), ('Robotaxi', 'ORG')]",0.238145,positive,20250819T080558,low
"Billionaires Buy a Brilliant Vanguard Index Fund That Could Turn $500 Per Month Into $442,400 With Help From the ""Magnificent Seven"" Stocks","This Vanguard index fund is heavily invested in the ""Magnificent Seven"" stocks, a group that includes Nvidia, Microsoft, Apple, Amazon, Meta Platforms, Alphabet, and Tesla.",[],[],"[('Vanguard', 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Meta Platforms', 'ORG'), ('Alphabet', 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 'ORG')]",0.423341,positive,20250819T080400,low
Tesla's 208 Megapacks Power xAI's Colossus 1 Supercomputer-Musk's AI Giant To Invest Over $40 Billion To Train Grok - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ,"Over 208 Tesla Inc. TSLA Megapacks Power Elon Musk's artificial intelligence company, xAI's Memphis Colossus 1 Supercomputer site, which supports the company's artificial intelligence model Grok amid a $40 billion investment.",[],[],"[('Tesla', 'ORG'), (""Colossus 1 Supercomputer-Musk's"", 'PERSON'), (""Megapacks Power Elon Musk's"", 'ORG'), ('Memphis Colossus 1 Supercomputer', 'ORG'), ('Grok', 'PERSON')]",0.135428,positive,20250819T063559,low
Elizabeth Warren Says Elon Musk's SpaceX Is Paying Less Tax Than You But Getting 'Billions' From The Government: Trump And GOP 'Rigged' The Tax Code - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ,Sen. Elizabeth Warren ( D-Mass. ) has accused Elon Musk's SpaceX of benefiting from billions in U.S. government contracts while paying little to no federal taxes.,[],[],"[('Elizabeth Warren', 'PERSON'), (""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON'), ('GOP', 'ORG'), ('Elizabeth Warren', 'PERSON'), (""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON')]",0.021808,positive,20250819T051257,low
Predicting the Next Rule Breaker Buyout,"Having a stock you own get acquired at a premium feels good at first, but what about the long-term gains that will be left behind when your chips are off the table?",[],[],"[('the Next Rule Breaker Buyout Having', 'ORG')]",0.170253,positive,20250819T040800,low
Tesla's revamped Model Y aimed at regaining mainland market share from rivals,"Tesla China has priced its six-seat Model Y variant about 30 per cent higher than its basic edition and has started accepting orders from customers who prefer spacious, long-range electric vehicles (EVs) for family use.",[],[],"[('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('Tesla China', 'ORG')]",0.056506,positive,20250819T040019,low
Should You Buy Nvidia Stock Before Aug. 27? Here's What History Suggests.,Nvidia stock is scheduled to report second-quarter earnings on Aug. 27.,[],[],"[('Nvidia', 'ORG')]",0.186948,positive,20250819T010000,low
"Trump 2.0 At 200 Days: Palantir Surges, Tesla Slumps - Palantir Technologies  ( NASDAQ:PLTR ) ",Palantir leads the S&P 500 with a stunning 160% gain in Trump's first 200 days. NRG Energy is the only stock to make the top 20 in both of Trump's terms. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise into opportunity.,[],[],"[('Palantir Surges', 'PERSON'), ('Tesla Slumps - Palantir', 'PERSON'), ('NASDAQ', 'ORG'), ('PLTR', 'ORG'), ('Palantir', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('NRG Energy', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.340477,positive,20250818T231149,low
Autonomous Vehicles Hit an Inflection Point; GPT-5 Is Here,Motley Fool Money checks in on some stock market news.,[],[],[],0.130658,positive,20250818T202200,low
"Tesla Stock Struggles For Clear Direction With Conflicting Sales, Demand Signals - Tesla  ( NASDAQ:TSLA ) ",Shares of Tesla are trading marginally higher Monday afternoon. Investors are weighing a mix of bullish institutional data against signs of weakening consumer demand in key European markets. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise into opportunity.,[],[],"[('Tesla Stock Struggles For', 'ORG')]",0.184379,positive,20250818T201543,low
"Bitcoin, Ethereum, XRP, Dogecoin Continue Slide Lower","Global cryptocurrency market capitalization dips 1.9% to $3.9 trillion. Trader notes Bitcoin's key short-term level to reclaim is around $117.5K, while another highlights the $114K-$116K zone as key area. Get more market-moving news first with AI-powered analysis that turns noise into opportunity.",[],[],"[('Bitcoin, Ethereum', 'ORG'), ('XRP', 'ORG'), ('Dogecoin Continue Slide Lower Global', 'ORG'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON')]",0.200504,positive,20250818T195125,low
